风云突变
记住 要成为真正的忍者
Remember, to be a true ninja,
你们必须与影子融为一体
you must become one with the shadows.
黑暗赋予忍者力量
Darkness gives the ninja power,
而光明会暴露忍者的行踪
while light reveals the ninja's presence.
现在
Now
你们能否熄灭这火焰
can you extinguish this flame
而不暴露自己?
without revealing yourselves?
声音太大 多纳泰罗
Too noisy, Donatello.
太笨拙了 米开朗基罗
Too clumsy, Michelangelo.
糟糕的选择 拉斐尔
Poor choice, Raphael.
干得好 李奥纳多
Well done, Leonardo.
老师的宠儿
Teacher's pet.
辍学的忍者
Ninja drop-out.
哦哟
Ooh!
孩子们
My sons.
啊 我的孩子们
Ah, My sons.
要成为真正的忍者
If you are to become true ninja,
你们必须更加努力
you must work harder.
你们的人生道路不会轻松
Your path in life will not be an easy one.
外面的世界对你们并不友好
The outside world will not be a friendly place for you.
你们四个如此与众不同
You four are different in ways
地上的人们不会理解的
the surface dwellers would never understand.
为了生存
To survive,
你们必须掌握我教的这些技巧
you must master these skills I teach you,
忍术中的潜行与隐遁之术
ninjitsu powers of stealth and secrecy.
你们必须成为影丸 影子武士
You must become kage, shadow warriors,
绝不能被外界所察觉
and you must never be discovered by the outside world.
嗯? 那是什么声音
Eh? What is that noise?
哇! 地震了
Whoa! Earthquake!
在纽约?
In New York?
有这个可能 但几率不大
Possible, but not likely.
那些是什么东西
What are those things?
纽约的蟑螂吗
New York City cockroaches?
不管是什么东西
Whatever they are,
它们来错地方了
they picked the wrong party to crash!
嘿 李奥
Hey, Leo,
快速出击
think fast!
我们得帮帮斯普林特老师
We have to help Master Splinter!
快来
Come on!
小心
Look out!
哦 不
Oh, no!
斯普林特老师
Master Splinter!
不
No!